<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ReGeX</string>

    <string name="match">Match</string>
    <string name="dmactch">Don\'t Match</string>
    <string name="regex">regex</string>
    <string name="title_activity_game">@string/app_name</string>
    <string name="solved">Solved with:</string>
    <string name="lvlup">Level up:</string>

    <string name="status">Status</string>
    <string name="round">Round</string>
    <!-- formerly "difficulty" -->
    <string name="diff">Level</string>
    <string name="score">Score</string>

    <string name="settings">Settings and Actions</string>
    <string name="clear">Reset game</string>
    <string name="confirm">Press to confirm</string>
    <string name="char_on">Turn char-bar on</string>
    <string name="char_off">Turn char-bar off</string>
    <string name="notif_on">Turn notifications on</string>
    <string name="notif_off">Turn notifications off</string>

    <string name="footer">ReGeX by @phikal, v1.2</string>

    <string name="title_activity_settings">@string/settings</string>

    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="source">Source</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="show_new">New</string>
    <string name="whats_newh">What\'s New</string>

    <string name="hello">ReGeX /ˈrɛːɡɛx/ is an android game, with a simple objective: Find a
       regular expression which does match certain strings, but doesn\'t match others.\n\n

        Depending on how long the expression is, how many regex characters you used and a few
        more variables, your score is generated. From the number of game and your score (high
        score and less games), the current level is calculated. The higher the level, the more
        complex the challenges become. There is no last or final level - it just goes on forever.\n\n

        Select game modes: either play random (fast and offline) or REDB [Regular Expression
        Database] (more challenging but online). Select and change modes in the settings\n\n

        Below I have added a link to a cheat-sheet on regular expression, for those unfamiliar
        with the syntax. There are tons of books and other tutorials on the subject, just
        use your search engine of choice and make sure you\'re looking for perl regular expressions.\n\n

        ---\n\n

        This app is free software (Licence: GPLv2+), and hosted on GitHub. If you want a new
        feature or found a bug, please submit a issue. Pull requests are also gladly appreciated.
    </string>

    <string name="random_game">Random Game</string>
    <string name="random_error">This shouldn\'t be happening&#8230;</string>

    <string name="redb_game">REDB Game</string>
    <string name="redb_error">Error requesting next task from server. Please change game mode.</string>
</resources>
